<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mental Flows</string>
    <string name="leftButton"><![CDATA[<]]></string>
    <string name="rightButton"><![CDATA[>]]></string>
    <string name="shareContent">Share</string>
    <string name="quote">Love begins from within, and flows from the heart. \n \n ~ Alex Hawkins</string>
    <string name="quote2">Breathe in for 4 seconds. Hold it. Breathe out for 3 seconds. Repeat. \n \n ~ Jhené Aiko</string>
    <string name="quote3">Life goes on. Let\'s live on. Life goes on. Let\'s live on. \n \n ~ Anonymous</string>
    <string name="quote4">Everything you need will be provided to you at the right place and the right time. \n \n ~ 444bunny</string>
    <string name="quote5">Great things come from hard work and perserverance. \n \n ~ Kobe Bryant</string>
    <string name="quote6">Appreciate where you are in life and how far you\'ve come. Gratitude attracts more blessings. \n \n ~ Carmelo Anthony</string>
    <string name="quote7">You are balanced. You are loved. You are winning. You are peaceful. You are alive. \n \n ~ 444bunny</string>
    <string name="quote8">All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them. \n \n ~ Walt Disney</string>
    <string name="quote9">Your angels are protecting you on your journey. Have faith and trust in what you are doing. \n \n ~ Anonymous</string>
    <string name="quote10">Focus on getting healthy, getting money and evolving your life. \n \n ~ GoldSuite</string>
    <string name="quote11">You are worthy of what you desire. You are resilient and capable of reaching your dreams. Take everything one day at a time. \n \n ~ Anonymous</string>
    <string name="quote12">The only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you haven’t found it yet, keep searching. It may find you. \n \n ~ Steve Jobs</string>
    <string name="quote13">The journey of a million miles begins with a single step. \n \n ~ Lao Tzu</string>
    <string name="quote14">Have faith in yourself and in the future. \n \n ~ Ted Kennedy</string>
    <string name="quote15">Do what you can, with what you have, where you are. \n \n ~ Theodore Roosevelt</string>
    <string name="quote16">You are a masterpiece. \n \n ~ Anonymous</string>
    <string name="quote17">Be a positive energy trampoline – absorb what you need and rebound more back. \n \n ~ Dave Carolan</string>
    <string name="quote18">Talent wins games, but teamwork and intelligence win championships. \n \n ~ Michael Jordan</string>
    <string name="quote19">Love your family, work super hard, live your passion. \n \n ~ Gary Vaynerchuk</string>
    <string name="quote20">Every breath we take, every step we make, can be filled with peace, joy and serenity. \n \n ~ Thich Nhat Hanh</string>
    <string name="quote21">You should feel beautiful and you should feel safe. What you surround yourself with should bring you peace of mind and peace of spirit. \n \n ~ Stacy London</string>
    <string name="quote22">Peace brings with it so many positive emotions that it is worth aiming for in all circumstances. \n \n ~ Estella Eliot</string>
    <string name="quote23">Peace is a journey of a thousand miles and it must be taken one step at a time. \n \n ~ Lyndon B. Johnson</string>
    <string name="quote24">When the power of love overcomes the love of power the world will know peace. \n \n ~ Jimi Hendrix</string>
    <string name="quote25">Success is not final; failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. \n \n ~ Winston S. Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote26">The successful warrior is the average man, with laser-like focus. \n \n ~ Bruce Lee</string>
    <string name="quote27">You yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe, deserve your love and affection. \n \n ~ Buddha</string>
    <string name="quote28">When you recover or discover something that nourishes your soul and brings joy, care enough about yourself to make room for it in your life. \n \n ~ Jean Shinoda Bolen</string>
    <string name="quote29">Keep calm and carry on. \n \n ~ Winston Churchill</string>
    <string name="quote30">Keep smiling, because life is a beautiful thing and there’s so much to smile about. \n \n ~ Marilyn Monroe</string>
    <string name="quote31">All life is an experiment. The more experiments you make, the better. \n \n ~ Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
    <string name="quote32">The most important thing is your family and taking care of each other and loving each other no matter what. \n \n ~ Stephen Curry</string>
    <string name="quote33">People like you are like sunshine for this world. Thank you for being the best version of yourself. \n \n ~ Michal Stawicki</string>
    <string name="quote34">To be successful, focus on your strengths and develop them. That\'s where you should pour your time, energy, and resources. \n \n ~ John C. Maxwell</string>
    <string name="quote35">I desire to have a life filled with positive energy and satisfaction of living authentically in my purpose. \n \n ~ Keya Briscoe</string>
    <string name="quote36">There’s a direct correlation between positive energy and positive results. \n \n ~ Joe Rogan</string>
    <string name="quote37">Passion is energy. Feel the power that comes from focusing on what excites you. \n \n ~ Oprah Winfrey</string>
    <string name="quote38">Wealth flows from energy and ideas. \n \n ~ William Feather</string>
    <string name="quote39">Positive thoughts, words, and actions create positive feelings. Positive feelings generate positive energy. \n \n ~ Nozer Kanga</string>
    <string name="quote40">Surround yourself with positive energy. \n \n ~ Anonymous</string>
</resources>